<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Making the Impossible, Possible]]></title>
  <link href="http://AYC726.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://AYC726.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-14T09:28:19-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://AYC726.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Alex Chiu]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[week 2 of flatiron]]></title>
    <link href="http://AYC726.github.io/blog/2013/10/08/week-2-of-flatiron/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-08T18:55:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://AYC726.github.io/blog/2013/10/08/week-2-of-flatiron</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hello alex</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let the adventure begin!]]></title>
    <link href="http://AYC726.github.io/blog/2013/09/27/hello-world/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-27T22:53:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://AYC726.github.io/blog/2013/09/27/hello-world</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First week of Flatiron school is complete and what a week it has been! From flying cross country and putting 7 years of my life in storage on September 21st, to starting school on September 23rd. I worked in the Boeing company for seven years; the first five years I was on the design team for the cabin interior of the 787. My proudest professional experience was from building something from nothing. Back in 2006 the 787 Dreamliner was just a paper airplane it existed in powerpoint presentations and excel spreadsheet.</p>

<p>I started working in the Boeing company on July 21st 2013 with the sole intend of building an amazing airplane! For the next five and a half years it was an amazing experience I worked with some of the best engineers in the world, learning how to build an airplane, travelled all over the world and even had time to run a marathon or two. After we built the airplane worked slowed down a lot, I wasn&rsquo;t building anything new and for going to work became boring.</p>

<p>For the next 12 weeks I will be immersed in code as I will try to build amazing things on web for all to see. Come follow me on this journey.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
